- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
kids: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
孩子们：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
All:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
[flute plays]
[长笛演奏]
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[surf rock music playing]
[冲浪摇滚音乐播放]
♪ ♪
[howling]
[嚎叫]
[owl hooting]
[猫头鹰叫声]
[insects chirping]
[昆虫鸣叫]
[ominous music]
[不祥的音乐]
♪ ♪
[cooing]
[咕咕声]
♪ ♪
- [grumbling]
- [抱怨]
[snail meows]
[蜗牛喵喵叫]
[meows]
[喵喵]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[laughter]
[笑声]
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [yawns, chokes]
- [打哈欠，窒息]
- Oh, boy, breakfast.
- 哦，男孩，早餐。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Hey, bad breakfast.
嘿嘿，早餐不好。
You go in my tummy.
你到我肚子里去吧。
[growls]
[咆哮]
Wow, you're the first
food to ever escape.
哇你是第一个
永远逃脱的食物。
I salute you, sir.
我向您致敬，先生。
[hisses]
[嘶嘶声]
[spits]
[吐口水]
Ooh, it's an envelope.
哦，这是一个信封。
Not my favorite flavor,
but whatever.
不是我最喜欢的味道，
但无论如何。
Oh, it's an opening envelope.
哦，这是一个可打开的信封。
Not an eating envelope.
不是吃信封。
[growls]
[咆哮]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
These things should
come with instructions.
这些东西应该
附带说明。
Maybe SpongeBob can help.
也许海绵宝宝可以帮忙。
He's good at stuff and things.
他很擅长东西。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
SpongeBob, can you open this
breakfast envelope for me?
海绵宝宝，你能打开这个吗
给我的早餐信封？
- You got a breakfast
envelope too?
- 你吃早餐了
信封也有吗？
How mysterious.
多么神秘啊。
Let's open them together.
让我们一起打开它们吧。
- Oh, yeah.
- 哦，是的。
- This letter's just snot
gonna open.
- 这封信只是鼻涕
要打开了
[laughs]
[笑]
Maybe it just needs
a little extra elbow grease.
也许只是需要
一点额外的肘部油脂。
- Whoa!
- See?
- 哇！
- 看？
What did I tell... ow.
我说什么了……哎哟。
My old Kamp Koral neckerchief?
我的旧 Kamp Koral 围巾？
Neat.
整洁的。
- Oh.
- 哦。
My old Kamp Koral underwear.
我的旧 Kamp Koral 内衣。
I haven't worn these in years.
我已经很多年没穿过这些了。
- Say, you think
anyone else got sent
- 说吧，你认为
其他人已发送
fun Kamp Koral memories?
有趣的坎普·科拉尔回忆吗？
Let's ask our
old bunkmate, Sandy.
来问问我们的
老室友桑迪。
- Ooh.
- 哦。
I think these memories
are cutting off
我想这些回忆
正在切断
the circulation to my brain.
我的大脑的循环。
[confetti toots]
[五彩纸屑嘟嘟]
- Envelope?
- 信封？
Oh, yeah, I got one of those.
哦，是的，我有其中之一。
Opened it up and got hit
right in the kisser
打开却被击中
就在接吻者身上
by my old braces.
我的旧牙套。
- Cool.
- 凉爽的。
Everyone got a prize.
每个人都获得了奖品。
Okay, mystery solved.
Goodbye.
好吧，谜团解开了。
再见。
- Wait, didn't you read
the letter in the envelope?
- 等等，你没读过吗
信封里的信？
- The letter?
- 那封信？
- "Do you miss the carefree
days of your youth?
——“你怀念无忧无虑的日子吗？
你的青春岁月？
"Well, pine away no more,
because you're invited
“好了，别再憔悴了，
因为你被邀请了
"to a killer reunion
at Kamp Koral.
“杀手重聚
在坎普科拉尔。
"Come relive your
childhood and party down.
“来重温你的
童年和聚会下来。
You'll just die
from all the fun."
你就会死掉
远离所有的乐趣。”
Signed, "X."
署名“X”。
Do you know what this means?
你知道这意味着什么吗？
- Yup.
- 是的。
"This" refers to a specific
person or object.
“这个”指的是具体的
人或物体。
- Yeah, that is right.
- 是的，没错。
But it also means we're
going back to Kamp Koral!
但这也意味着我们
回到坎普科拉尔！
- Yeehaw! High five.
- 耶哈！高五。
- High five.
- 高五。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- Get swole!
- 膨胀起来！
Huh?
啊？
[school bell rings]
- Oh.
[放学铃声响起]
- 哦。
- It's just as good as...
- Ah!
- 这就像...一样好
- 啊！
[laughing]
[笑]
[confetti toots]
- [grunts]
[五彩纸屑嘟嘟]
- [咕哝]
- Oh!
- 哦！
- Meep.
[confetti tooting]
- 米普。
[五彩纸屑鸣响]
- Meep.
- 米普。
- Moop.
- 穆普。
Mop.
拖把。
- [grumbling]
- [抱怨]
[confetti toots]
[五彩纸屑嘟嘟]
Huh?
啊？
[mumbling]
[咕哝]
I ain't going
to some dumb reunion
我不去
一些愚蠢的重聚
at the old summer camp.
在老夏令营。
I barely shut that place
down in time to avoid
我几乎没有关闭那个地方
及时下降以避免
all those health code
violations.
所有这些健康码
违规行为。
Huh?
啊？
I'd know this nickel anywhere.
我在任何地方都会认识这枚五分钱。
"P.S., Look familiar?
“P.S.，你看起来很眼熟吗？
Come and get the rest
if you dare."
过来拿剩下的
如果你敢的话。”
[gasps]
Sweet Neptune!
[喘气]
甜蜜的海王星！
A map to me lost camp nickels.
一张地图给我丢了营地镍币。
The ones I hid so well,
even I forgot where I hid 'em.
那些我隐藏得很好的人，
连我都忘了我把它们藏在哪里了。
Me and me money.
我和我的钱。
Now that's a reunion
worth attending.
现在这就是重逢
值得参加。
[laughs]
[笑]
- Oh, boy, I can't wait
to go back to Kamp Koral.
- 哦，孩子，我等不及了
回到坎普科拉尔。
- Yeah. But how are
we gonna get there?
- 是的。但怎么样
我们能到达那里吗？
My unicycle is in the shop.
我的独轮车在店里。
- Well...
- I know.
- 嗯...
- 我知道。
We could prance.
我们可以腾跃。
- Oh, boy, I haven't
pranced in ages.
-哦，孩子，我还没有
多年来一直欢腾。
Both: ♪ La la la la la la ♪
两人：♪ 啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
all: ♪ La la la la la la ♪
全体：♪ 啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
- Just get on the bus.
- 上公共汽车就可以了。
- Oh, yeah, the bus.
- 哦，是的，公共汽车。
- Yeah, I do suppose
that makes sense.
- 是的，我确实认为
这是有道理的。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [pants] Wait for me, dudes.
- [裤子]等我，伙计们。
- And that's why Barnacle Boy,
with both hands...
- 这就是为什么藤壶男孩，
用双手...
[chattering]
[喋喋不休]
[meeping]
[嘀咕]
[laughter]
[笑声]
♪ ♪
- [laughing]
- [笑]
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
[laughter]
[笑声]
- What are you looking at, boyo?
- 你在看什么，男孩？
- [sighs]
You haven't changed a bit
- [叹气]
你一点也没变
since camp, Mr. Krabs.
自从营地以来，蟹老板。
Greetings, fellow campers.
各位营员们，大家好。
I'd like to personally thank
我想亲自感谢
whoever invited us
to the big reunion.
无论谁邀请我们
到大团聚。
So who was it?
那是谁呢？
- Not me.
- 不是我。
- Oh, well, we're sure
to when we get there.
- 哦，好吧，我们确定
到我们到达那里的时候。
Next stop, Camp Money!
[cash register dings]
下一站，钱营！
[收银机叮叮声]
- Eugene.
- 尤金.
- I mean Kamp Koral.
- 我的意思是坎普·科拉尔。
[cheering]
[欢呼]
- Yeah!
- 是的！
Whoo-hoo!
呼呼！
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- Ah, good old Kamp Koral.
- 啊，好老的坎普·科拉尔。
[ominous music]
[不祥的音乐]
♪ ♪
It seems different somehow.
似乎有些不同。
- Looks like they
changed the name to Kaka.
- 看起来他们
改名为卡卡。
- Well, I must say,
- 嗯，我必须说，
the place has really
gone to pot.
这个地方确实有
去锅了。
- Well, I think
someone is pulling
- 嗯，我想
有人在拉
a fast one with this reunion.
这次重聚是一个快速的过程。
- Don't listen to her,
little nickel.
- 别听她的
小镍。
We'll find your friends soon.
我们很快就会找到你的朋友。
♪ ♪
- This place is, like,
way smaller than I remember.
- 这个地方就像，
比我记忆中的小得多。
- It's not smaller.
- 它并不小。
You're just bigger.
你只是更大了。
But it is a lot crummier.
但它要糟糕得多。
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- All right, I think this
joke has gone far enough.
- 好吧，我想这个
玩笑已经开得够远了。
Everyone, back on the bus.
各位，回到巴士上。
We are not staying here.
我们不住在这里。
[tires hissing]
[轮胎嘶嘶声]
[clanging]
[叮叮当当]
Not to worry, I'll get the tools
不用担心，我会去拿工具的
and we'll put
the wheels back on.
我们将把
轮子重新启动。
[rustling]
[沙沙声]
Maybe we could just...
也许我们可以...
- Well, looks like we're walking
- 嗯，看起来我们正在走路
back across the bridge.
过桥回来。
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
♪ ♪
- Oh, no.
- 哦，不。
We'll have to use
the old tunnel.
我们必须使用
旧隧道。
♪ ♪
That's okay.
没关系。
To the hot air balloon field.
前往热气球场。
- We're trapped!
- 我们被困住了！
- Every way to get is gone.
- 所有获得的方法都消失了。
- Maybe for the
likes of you rabble.
- 也许是为了
喜欢你们这些乌合之众。
Regigilled, commence
Operation Wealth Extraction.
重新调整，开始
财富提取行动。
- What in tarnation?
- 塔尼翁什么？
- What is that?
- 那是什么？
- What is it?
- 这是什么？
- Huh?
- 啊？
- Wait!
- 等待！
[shouting]
[喊叫]
- Hurry, Regigilled.
- 快点，雷吉利德。
[clamoring]
[叫喊]
Look what you've done to
my third favorite helicopter.
看看你做了什么
我第三喜欢的直升机。
I am offended.
我很生气。
- Hey, at least no one
got hurt, right?
- 嘿，至少没有人
受伤了，对吧？
- Oh, finally alone.
- 哦，终于一个人了。
Now to find me booty.
现在来给我找战利品。
Let's see.
让我们来看看。
100 paces south.
向南100步。
Okay.
好的。
One, two, three.
一二三。
[banging]
[砰砰]
Hey, out of my way, cabin.
嘿，别挡我的路，小屋。
[cabin whimpering]
[机舱呜咽声]
Stupid cabin.
愚蠢的小屋。
Four, five.
四、五。
- What should we do now,
Mr. Krabs?
- 我们现在应该做什么，
蟹老板？
Mr. Krabs?
- Has anyone seen Eugene?
- 有人见过尤金吗？
- I think I saw him walk off
with something under his arm.
- 我想我看见他走开了
腋下夹着什么东西。
- If my dad had a newspaper
under his arm when he left,
- 如果我爸爸有一份报纸
离开时夹在腋下，
we won't see him
for a couple of hours.
我们不会见到他
几个小时。
- 98, 99, 100.
- 98、99、100。
Ooh, X marks the spot.
哦，X 标记了位置。
[laughing]
[笑]
Found it!
找到了！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Ooh, now to get
what's coming to me.
哦，现在要得到
我会发生什么。
Huh?
啊？
[screaming]
[尖叫]
- Hey, that sounds
like Mr. Krabs...
- 嘿，听起来
就像蟹老板一样...
having a blast.
玩得很开心。
Good ol' Camp Master Krabs.
好蟹蟹营长。
He knows how to have fun.
他知道如何享受乐趣。
Whoo-hoo!
[cheering]
呼呼！
[欢呼]
[engine revving]
[发动机转速]
- What's that?
- 那是什么？
- Maybe it's another bus
to take us home.
- 也许是另一辆巴士
带我们回家。
[heavy metal music]
[重金属音乐]
♪ ♪
Nurse Helga!
赫尔加护士！
- It is me.
- 是我。
I am here for the reunion.
我是来参加团聚的。
- What'd I miss?
- 我错过了什么？
- Oh.
- 哦。
And it looks like I
got here just in time.
而且看起来我
来得正是时候。
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
- Come back, bubby
with the boo boo.
- 回来吧，巴比
与嘘声。
- Looks like Kamp Koral is
reopened for business.
- 看起来坎普·科拉尔是
重新营业。
[cheering]
[欢呼]
[indistinct chattering]
[模糊不清的喋喋不休]
- Well, gang, if we're
gonna be stuck here,
- 好吧，伙计们，如果我们
会被困在这里
we might as well enjoy
being back in camp.
我们不妨享受
回到营地。
♪ Jump up and cheer
for old Kamp Koral ♪
♪ 跳起来欢呼
献给老坎普·科拉尔 ♪
♪ where the food is bad
and tastes abnormal ♪
♪ 食物不好的地方
而且味道异常♪
♪ The bunks are
filled with bugs ♪
♪ 铺位是
充满虫子♪
♪ And the woods are
paranormal ♪
♪ 树林里
超自然现象♪
♪ But we love it here in camp,
so there will be no quarrel ♪
♪ 但我们喜欢这里的营地，
这样就不会吵架了♪
[grumbling]
[抱怨]
- Is this really our old cabin?
- 这真的是我们的旧小屋吗？
Regigilled, door.
重装，门。
- As you wish.
- 如你所愿。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- Oh, heavens.
- 哦，天哪。
Disgusting.
恶心。
Outrageous.
太离谱了。
Our beautiful cabin's gone
from chateau to shanty.
我们美丽的小屋不见了
从城堡到棚户区。
[lilting harpsichord music]
[轻快的羽管键琴音乐]
♪ ♪
- Eww.
- 呃。
- Oh, my.
- Oh.
- 哦，天哪。
- 哦。
Regigilled!
重新调整！
- As you wish.
- 如你所愿。
Hmm hmm hmm.
嗯嗯嗯。
- It's a bit lumpier
than I remember.
- 有点块状
比我记得的还要多。
- [growling]
- [咆哮]
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
- This place is haunted!
- 这个地方闹鬼！
[clock dings]
[钟声]
Oh. Regigilled!
哦。重新调整！
- As you wish.
- 如你所愿。
Hmm hmm hmm.
嗯嗯嗯。
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
- Will there be anything else?
-还会有别的事吗？
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
- As you wish.
- 如你所愿。
- [evil laughter]
- [邪恶的笑声]
- Thanks for removing
that helicopter thingy.
- 感谢您删除
那个直升机的东西。
But now my stomach
is empty again.
但现在我的胃
又是空的。
[sniffing]
[嗅嗅]
Food!
食物！
- Imbeciles.
- 低能儿。
[flies buzzing]
[苍蝇嗡嗡声]
Ay.
哎呀。
This cabin was
spotless when I left.
这间小屋是
我离开时一尘不染。
[gasps]
[喘气]
My scalpels, my clamps,
我的手术刀，我的夹子，
my slashing tools... all gone!
我的砍刀工具……全没了！
Huh?
啊？
[rustling]
[沙沙声]
Who's there?
谁在那里？
Does someone have a boo boo?
有人有嘘声吗？
Do you need Nurse Helga
to put you back together?
你需要赫尔加护士吗
让你们重新在一起？
Phew.
唷。
[screaming]
[尖叫]
- [evil laughter]
- [邪恶的笑声]
- Will you please keep it down?
- 请你小声点好吗？
- Shh.
- 嘘。
That was obviously a werewolf.
那分明就是一个狼人。
- But it's daytime,
and there's no moon.
- 但现在是白天
而且没有月亮。
- Then it must be some sort
of marauding camp creeper.
- 那么一定是某种
掠夺营地爬行者。
- We have bigger problems.
- 我们有更大的问题。
It appears there's
no mechanism for zipping.
看来有
没有拉链机制。
- Then let's improvise.
- 那么我们来即兴发挥吧。
- Yeah.
- 是的。
[laughter]
[笑声]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Uh-oh.
- 呃哦。
[screaming]
[尖叫]
Ow.
噢。
[screams]
[尖叫声]
My posterior has suffered
a double cranial concussion.
我的后背已受苦
双颅脑震荡。
- It's not looking so good.
- 看起来不太好。
- Oh, no, his butt is wiped out.
- 哦，不，他的屁股已经被毁掉了。
[screaming]
[尖叫]
- Thank you, Kevin.
- 谢谢你，凯文。
But I'm sure my butt
doesn't look that bad.
但我确信我的屁股
看起来没那么糟糕。
- Hey, where's Kevin?
- 嘿，凯文在哪儿？
Kevin, quit goofing around.
凯文，别再胡闹了。
[screams]
[尖叫声]
I got a feeling there's
something supernatural
我有一种感觉
超自然的东西
going on around here.
这里正在发生。
- I've got a feeling too.
- 我也有一种感觉。
In my glutes.
在我的臀部。
[sobs]
[抽泣]
- [sniffing]
- [嗅嗅]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
Food. Snacks.
食物。零食。
Oof!
钱币！
The Krusty Kanteen!
库斯蒂坎廷！
Hug!
拥抱！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Let no man say I didn't try.
不要让任何人说我没有尝试过。
[rustling]
Huh?
[沙沙声]
啊？
Is someone blorping at me?
有人对我吹气吗？
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Just one more drum of expired
Chum left to illegally dump.
- 只剩一桶过期了
密友留下来非法倾倒垃圾。
- I don't know why
you insisted on coming
- 我不知道为什么
你坚持要来
all the way out here
just to dump some Chum.
一直到这里
只是为了甩掉一些密友。
- Because not even
an idiot would
- 因为甚至没有
一个白痴会
come all the way out here.
千里迢迢来到这里。
- Hi, Mr. Plankton.
- 嗨，浮游生物先生。
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
Oh, it's you.
哦，是你。
What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
[screams]
[尖叫声]
- We're here for the party.
- 我们是来参加聚会的。
Didn't you get an invite
to the Kamp Koral reunion?
你没有收到邀请吗
参加 Kamp Koral 聚会？
- Reunion?
- 重聚？
Why would I go to
a dumb daycare reunion?
我为什么要去
愚蠢的日托聚会？
[screams]
[尖叫声]
- 'Cause we're getting hungry.
- 因为我们饿了。
And you were the cook here once.
你曾经是这里的厨师。
So why don't you
get cookin', cook?
那你为什么不
做饭吧，做饭吗？
- Cook?
- 厨师？
I'll cook your face.
我来煮你的脸。
- Easy, tiger.
- 简单，老虎。
Let's play along
so they don't report us.
我们一起玩吧
所以他们不会举报我们。
- Ugh, fine.
- 呃，好吧。
Come and get it!
快过来取！
You lousy punks.
你们这些糟糕的小混混。
- You're not really
gonna feed them
- 你不是真的
会喂他们
this putrid Chum, are you?
这个腐烂的密友，是你吗？
- Sure.
- 当然。
Polluting campers is
more environmentally conscious
污染露营者的是
更有环保意识
than polluting the lake,
right, noodle brain?
比起污染湖泊，
对吧，面条脑？
- Mmm. Brain noodles.
- 嗯。脑面条。
[grumbling]
[抱怨]
[growls]
[咆哮]
- Suddenly I'm not hungry.
- 突然我不饿了。
- Bleh.
- 布莱赫。
Me neither.
我也不。
Hey, does anybody want
to play some volleyball?
嘿嘿，有人要吗
打排球吗？
- Does a one-legged duck
swim in circles?
- 是一只单腿鸭子吗
绕圈游？
[cheering]
[欢呼]
- Hey, wait for me!
- 嘿，等等我！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- [chomping]
- [咀嚼]
Ahh.
啊。
- Meep.
- 米普。
- [muffled gagging]
- [低声作呕]
- Yuck.
- 恶心。
I've been sullied.
我已经被玷污了
I need a shower.
我需要洗个澡。
[sobs]
[抽泣]
- Wait! Don't shower!
- 等待！不要洗澡！
Have you never seen
a horror movie?
你没见过吗
恐怖电影？
The creeper will get you!
爬行者会抓住你的！
[distant howling]
[远处的嚎叫]
I'm alone.
我还是孤单一人。
That's against
the horror movie rules too.
那是反对
恐怖电影也有规则。
[whimpering]
[呜咽]
- [retches]
- [干呕]
Meep. Meep. Meep!
米普。米普。米普！
- Meep. Meep. Meep.
- 米普。米普。米普。
- [evil laughter]
- [邪恶的笑声]
- [whistles]
- [口哨]
- Meep!
- 米普！
- [evil laughter]
- [邪恶的笑声]
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- Ooh, that's good.
- 哦，那很好。
I can never get back there.
我永远无法回到那里。
♪ ♪
Harvey, is that you?
哈维，是你吗？
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
[gasps]
[喘气]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[whimpering]
[呜咽]
So clean.
这么干净。
So terrifyingly clean.
干净得可怕。
[screaming]
[尖叫]
♪ ♪
So clean.
这么干净。
- [evil laughter]
- [邪恶的笑声]
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
[cheering]
[欢呼]
- While we're stuck
at this dirty camp,
- 当我们陷入困境时
在这个肮脏的营地里，
who's gonna be
the volleyball champ?
谁会是
排球冠军？
- Get ready.
- 准备好。
I call this serve
the "Hey, mister,
我称之为服务
“嘿，先生，
can we get our
ball back, please?"
我们能得到我们的
请回球吧？”
[grunts]
- Ow!
[咕哝]
- 噢！
- Owie, wowie,
that's gotta stingy.
- 奥伊，哇伊，
那就太小气了
Hit her back, whack attack,
let's go Dinghies!
打她的背，重击攻击，
我们去小艇吧！
- I got it!
- 我得到了它！
Ah.
啊。
[ominous music]
[不祥的音乐]
Oh, a wise guy, eh?
哦，一个聪明人，是吗？
[both grunting]
[两人都咕哝着]
- [evil laughter]
- [邪恶的笑声]
- [laughing]
- [笑]
- Whatcha laughin' at?
- 笑什么？
- I'm just laughing because
the woods are laughing.
- 我只是笑因为
树林在笑。
[ominous music]
[不祥的音乐]
♪ ♪
- Hey, where's Mo?
- 嘿，莫在哪儿？
- Obviously incinerated by me.
- 显然是被我烧毁了。
- I think you mean intimidated.
- 我认为你的意思是受到恐吓。
- Yeah.
- 是的。
- Whatever.
- 任何。
We're still gonna
destroy you, dude.
我们还是要
毁了你，伙计。
Hey, Tall Tail,
you're subbed in.
嘿，高尾巴，
你被替换了。
- Come on, Tall Tail.
- 来吧，高尾巴。
Pull up your socks.
拉起你的袜子。
Smash that ball,
win it all, let's go jocks!
击碎那个球，
赢得一切，让我们加油！
- I call this serve Deep Impact.
- 我称之为“深度影响”发球。
Whoop!
哎哟！
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
[both grunt]
[两人咕哝]
- Huh?
- 啊？
[groans]
[呻吟]
Barely hit me.
差一点就打到我了。
- I'll get it.
- 我会得到它。
- I'll come with you.
- 我跟你一起去。
- [evil laughter]
- [邪恶的笑声]
- [laughing]
- [笑]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
- Mr. Krabs, the Yacht Cabin,
- 蟹老板先生，游艇小屋，
Kevin, Nurse Helga,
凯文，赫尔加护士，
the Anchovies, Bubble Bass,
and now the jocks
凤尾鱼、泡泡鲈鱼、
现在运动员们
have all mysteriously
disappeared.
都神秘地拥有
消失了。
- Oh, they're probably
just somewhere having fun.
- 哦，他们可能是
只是在某个地方玩得开心。
Ahh!
啊！
- Somewhere in their graves.
- 在他们坟墓的某个地方。
- I'm sure there's a perfectly
good, highly reasonable,
- 我确信有一个完美的
很好，非常合理，
scientifically proven
explanation
科学证明
解释
for their disappearances.
对于他们的失踪。
And besides, not all
the jocks are gone.
此外，并非所有
运动员们都走了。
Tall Tail is still...
高尾还是...
jumping flap jacks, he's gone!
跳襟翼开合，他走了！
- The camp creeper
strikes again.
- 营地爬行者
再次罢工。
- This reunion's not so fun.
- 这次重聚没那么有趣。
The cheerleader's
always the next one.
啦啦队长的
总是下一个。
Gimme a C-R-Y!
给我一个 C-R-Y！
[crying]
[哭泣]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]